Guide to the Actors' Fund of America Photographs and Audio-Visual Materials. PHOTOS.240
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Photographs, 1880-2006., 1960-2000
  - Subseries I-A: Events and Places, 1888-2006., 1970-2000
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Actors' Equity Tour of Facility (color), undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Artist Renderings (b&w), undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Dedication Ceremony (b&w), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Dedication Ceremony (color), Dec 15, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Exterior (b&w), undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Groundbreaking (b&w), 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Groundbreaking and Construction (b&w), 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Interior (b&w), undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Interior (color), undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Residents (b&w), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Extended Care Facility: Residents (color), undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Floor Plan (copy photographs) (b&w), undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Founder's Day Picnic (color), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Founder's Day Picnic (color), 1988 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Founder's Day Picnic (color), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Actors' Fund Home: "It Runs in the Family" Filming (with Kirk and Michael Douglas) (color), undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Percy Williams Wing I (b&w), undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Percy Williams Wing II (b&w), undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Special Performances for Residents: "Much Ado About Nothing" (produced by National Players) (b&w), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Special Performances for Residents: "One Mo' Time" (produced by American Theatre Wing) (b&w), Oct 23, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Special Performances for Residents: "Singing in the Rain" (produced by American Theatre Wing) (color), Feb 1986 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Special Performances for Residents: "Sweeney Todd" (produced by American Theatre Company) (color), Oct 24, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Actor's Fund Home, Staten Island, New York (copy photographs) (b&w), undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Actors' Fund Home, Staten Island, New York: Official Opening (with Joseph Jefferson as main speaker) (b&w), May 5, 1902 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors (b&w), undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors (color), undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: American Theatre Wing (color), undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Board of Trustees (b&w), Jun 22, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Board of Trustees (b&w), Apr 24, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Board of Trustees (b&w), Dec 1976 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Board of Trustees (b&w), Apr 4, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Board of Trustees (b&w), undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Brendan Byrne (Governor of New Jersey) (b&w), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Gloria Swanson (b&w), Jan 18, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Gwen Verdon (b&w), Oct 23, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: John Strasburg (b&w), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Lillian Gish and Jack Pearl (b&w), 1970 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Robert Morse and Maureen Stapleton (b&w), Dec 11, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Actors' Fund Home: Visitors: Unidentified Russian Folksinger (b&w), 1989 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Alex H. Cohen and Hildy Parks (b&w); Close-up of Medal, May 1985 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Angela Lansbury (b&w), Apr 21, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Armina Marshall (b&w), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Clive Barnes (b&w), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Danny Kaye and Richard Rodgers (Central Park) (b&w), Apr 1971 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Debbie Reynolds (b&w), Feb 2, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Ethel Merman (b&w), Oct 1971 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Harold Prince (b&w), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Joseph Papp (b&w), Apr 17, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Neil Simon (b&w), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Newbold Morris (b&w), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Robert F. Wagner, Jr. (b&w), 1962 (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Ronald Reagan (b&w), undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: The Shubert Organization, Bernard Jacobs and Gerard Schoenfeld (b&w), Nov 18, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: The Shubert Organization, Bernard Jacobs and Gerard Schoenfeld: Photographs of Medals Given (b&w), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Vincent Sardi (b&w), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Warren P. Munsell (b&w), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Actors' Fund Medal & New York City Award Presentation: Walter Vincent (b&w), Jun 8, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Actors' Fund Medal Presentation: Unidentified Recipient (b&w), undated (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Actors' Fund Memorial Day Activities with Ethel Barrymore (b&w), Dec 5, 1919 (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - Actors' Fund Souvenir Spoon (b&w), Oct 1975-1980 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Actors' Fund Week: Mayoral Proclamations (Impellitari & Wagner) (b&w), undated, 1952-1957 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Actors' Fund Women's Committee Lunch (b&w), Oct 19, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Actors' Work Program: College/School Fair (color), 1999 (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - Actors' Work Program: Unidentified Event Shot by Jerry Speier (b&w), 2000 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - A&E Network Salutes Theatre in America - Reception with Production Shots from "Stage for a Nation" (A&E Network Documentary about National Theatre) (b&w), Oct-Nov 1987 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Aging in America Morningside House: President's Dinner (honoring Vermont Royster, Joshua Logan and Nedda Harrigan Logan), May 6, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - AIDS & the Arts Conference (color), Jun 28, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - American Federation of Musicians, Local 802: Local 802 Fights AIDS (b&w), 1992 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - "Annie" Christmas Party (b&w), 1978 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Annual Meeting (b&w), 1972 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Annual Meeting: Royal Theater (b&w), 1973 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Annual Meeting (color), 1980 (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - Annual Meeting (b&w), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Annual Meeting (b&w), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Annual Meeting (color), 1991 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Annual Meeting (b&w), undated (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) I (b&w), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) II (b&w), 1974-1975 (Box 3, Box 117)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) (b&w), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) (b&w), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) (b&w), 1981 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) (b&w), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) (color), 1987 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) (b&w), 1988 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) I (b&w), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) II (b&w), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for) III (b&w), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Annual Report (photopraphs used or shot for) (color), undated (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for): AIDS Initiative and Nursing Home Clients (b&w), ca. 1997 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for): Photographs for Profiles (b&w), ca. 1998 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Annual Report (photographs used or shot for): Photographs Lent to Bree Coven by Sarah Meehan (b&w), 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Association of Theatrical Press Agents and Managers: Luncheon and Tour of Actors' Fund Home, May 11, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Auction (b&w), Apr 1973 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Auction (color), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Auction (b&w), undated (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Auction of 1000 Stars I (color), May 2000 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Auction of 1000 Stars II (color), May 2000 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Auction of 1000 Stars (color), 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - Auction: Nearly New Shop, 802 Ninth Ave, New York City (b&w), undated (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - Auction: Sotheby Parke Bernet Theatrical Memorabilia (b&w), Apr 12, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 139)
    - Aurora Residence, New York City: Artist Rendering (color), undated (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Aurora Residence, New York City: Exterior, Interior and Offices (ca. Christmas) (color), Dec-Jan 2000 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - Aurora Residence, New York City: International Interior Design Association - Fundraising Booth (color), undated (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Aurora Residence, New York City: Visitors (b&w), Jun 15, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Baldoria Restaurant, Party at (color), 2004 (Box 3, Folder 144)
    - Barney's, Actors' Fund Party at (b&w), Sep 24, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Barrymore Stamp Commemoration (b&w), Jun 8, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 146)
    - Barrymore Stamp Commemoration (color), Jun 8, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 147)
    - Bazaar (b&w), Spring 1976 (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - Bazaar I (b&w), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - Bazaar II (b&w), 1978 (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - Bazaar: Alfred Lunt Display Window (b&w), 1977 (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - Bazaar: B-Group (b&w), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 152)
    - Bazaar: Booths (b&w), undated (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Bazaar: Display Window (b&w), undated (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Bazaar: Harold Friedlander Memorial Window (b&w), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Bazaar: Photographs of Items for Sale at (color), undated (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Bazaar: Photographs for Sale at (b&w), undated (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - Benefit: Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday) (b&w) I, Jun 22, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - Benefit: Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday) (b&w) II, Jun 22, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Benefit: Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday) (b&w) III, Jun 22, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Benefit: Happy Birthday, Mr. Abbott (George Abbott 100th Birthday): Citation Presented to George Abbott, Jun 22, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Benefit: "Julius Caesar" at Beechwood Amphitheater, Hollywood (copy photographs) (b&w), May 20, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Benefit: Parade of Stars (b&w), undated (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Benefit: "Salute to Entertainment": Celebrities (Alisa Gyse and Arnetia Walker) (b&w), Jun 1992 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Benefit: Unidentified: Co-sponsored by Pfizer, Inc. (color), Aug 10, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Benefit Concert: "Chess" (3rd Annual) (color), Sep 22, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 166)
    - Benefit Concert: "First You Dream: A Tribute to Courage" (color), Jun 12, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Benefit Concert: "Funny Girl!" (2nd Annual) (color), Sep 23, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 168)
    - Benefit Concert: "Nothing Like a Dame" (b&w), Feb 24, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 169)
    - Benefit Concert: "Nothing Like a Dame" (color), Feb 24, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 170)
    - Benefit Concert: "Nothing Like a Dame" (b&w), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Benefit Concert: "Nothing Like a Dame" (color), 1998 (Box 4, Folder 172)
    - Benefit Concert: "Nothing Like a Dame" (color), Mar 12, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Benefit Performance: "700 Sundays" (color), Feb 22, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Benefit Performance: "Anything Goes": Champagne Reception with Company (b&w), Apr 17, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Benefit Performance: "Avenue Q" (color), Dec 11, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Benefit Performance: "Blunt Speaking" (color), Nov 9, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Benefit Performance: "La Boheme" (color), May 11, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Benefit Performance: "Bon Apetit" (with Jean Stapleton) (b&w), Nov 11, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 179)
    - Benefit Performance: "Brooklyn" (color), Jan 23, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Benefit Performance: "Cats" (b&w), 1985 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Benefit Performance: "Cats" (b&w), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Benefit Performance: "A Christmas Carol" (b&w), Dec 12, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Benefit Performance: "A Christmas Carol" (b&w), 1990 (Box 4, Folder 184)
    - Benefit Performance: "The Crucible" (color), Jun 9, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Benefit Performance: "The Dead" (color), Feb 13, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Benefit Performance: "Frankie and Johnny" (color), Oct 27, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Benefit Performance: "The Graduate" (color), Aug 25, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Benefit Performance: "Hairspray" (color), Jan 26, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Benefit Performance: "Hedda Gabler" (color), Jan 13, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Benefit Performance: "Kiss Me, Kate" (color), Mar 12, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Benefit Performance: "The Lion King" (color), Oct 22, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Benefit Performance: "Long Day's Journey Into Night" (color), Aug 26, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Benefit Performance: "Mama Mia!" (color), Dec 8, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Benefit Performance: "Man of La Mancha" (color), Apr 6, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Benefit Performance: "Man of La Mancha," Los Angeles, California (b&w), May 15, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Benefit Performance: "Mario Cantone: Laugh Whore" (color), Jan 3, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Benefit Performance: "Metamorphoses" (color), Jun 23, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Benefit Performance: "A Moon for the Misbegotten" (color), Jun 25, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Benefit Performance: "Movin' Out" (color), Jan 19, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Benefit Performance: "Night Mother" (color), Jan 12, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Benefit Performance: "Nine" (color), Sep 9, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Benefit Performance: "Princess and Black-Eyed Pea" (color), Sep 25, 1999-Sep 25, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Benefit Performance: "The Producers" (color), 2001 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Benefit Performance: "The Producers" (color), Jun 1, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Benefit Performance: "Shear Madness," Chicago, Illinois (b&w), Apr 1, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Benefit Performance: "Shear Madness," Chicago, Illinois (color), Apr 1, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Benefit Performance: "Shear Madness," Chicago, Illinois: Press Kit (b&w), Apr 1, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Benefit Performance: "Talking Lens" (color), Sep 22, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Benefit Performance: "Thoroughly Modern Millie" (color), Aug 11, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Benefit Performance: "Uncle Vanya" (b&w), Jul 29, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Benefit Performance: "Urinetown" (color), Aug 18, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 212)
    - Benefit Performance: "Waiting in the Wings" (color), Feb 27, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Benefit Performance: "WIT-LA" (color), Feb 13, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Benefit Performance?: "Annie" (color), Jun 17, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Benefit Performance?: "Dreamgirls" (b&w), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Benefit Performance?: "Dreamgirls" (color), Oct 2001 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Benefit Performance?: "The Last Session" (color), undated (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Benefit Performance?: "The Producers" (color), 2006 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Benefit Performance?: "Talking Lens" (color), 2002 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Benefit Reading: "All About Eve": Los Angeles, California (color), Mar 30, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1966 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1973 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1978 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), 1983 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive (b&w), undated (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive: Canastel's 25th Annual Dinner for Nedda Logan (b&w), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive: Los Angeles, California (b&w), 1981-1987 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive: Los Angeles, California (color), 1990 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive: Midwest (b&w), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Blood Bank/Blood Drive: Shubert Alley (b&w), Aug 18, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Bread Basket Campaign: Actors' Fund Week (b&w), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Bread Basket Campaign: Actors' Fund Week (b&w), undated (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Bread Basket Campaign: Launching at Act I (b&w), 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Bread Basket Campaign: Launching at Pub Theatrical and Others (b&w), 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Break a Leg Award: Ann Miller and Mickey Rooney: "Sugar Babies" (b&w), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Break a Leg Award: Anthony Quinn (b&w), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Break a Leg Award: Carol Channing and Mary Martin (b&w), Apr 2, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Break a Leg Award: Cast of "Dreamgirls" (b&w), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Break a Leg Award: Cast of "You Can't Take It with You" (b&w), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Break a Leg Award: Rockettes (b&w), Dec 18, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Break a Leg Award: Tommy Tune and Twiggy: "My One and Only" (b&w), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Break a Leg Award: Unidentified Recipients (b&w), undated (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Broadway Cares/Equity Fights AIDS Presents Check to Actors' Fund (color), May 2003 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Broadway Show League at St. Albans Hospital (b&w), 1969 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Camp Beverly Hills (b&w), undated (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - A Century of the Actors' Fund in Pictures: Resource Photographs and Documents (b&w), 1882-1982 (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - "A Chorus Line" (Movie) Premiere (b&w), Dec 9, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - "A Chorus Line" (Movie) Premiere, Poster for (color), Dec 9, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - "A Christmas Carol": Reception at Sardi's Restaurant, New York (b&w), Dec 15, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - "A Christmas Carol": Reception at Sardi's Restaurant, New York (color), Dec 15, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Directors' Guild: Picnic (b&w), undated (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Dorothy Patten Awards (b&w), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Dorothy Patten Awards (color), 1984 (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - Drama Desk Luncheon: Salute to Old Stars (b&w), May 16, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - Emmy Awards (b&w), May 1989 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - Fraunces Tavern, Boxing Day Dinner Party at (b&w), Dec 26, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Gala (b&w), Nov 2, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Gala (color), Nov 1999 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Gala: Annual Holiday Gala (b&w), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Gala: Annual Holiday Gala (color), Dec 11, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Gala: Dance Gala (b&w), Sep 21, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Gala: Dance Gala, Press Conference Announcing (b&w), Jun 25, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Gala: Honoring James Nederlander at the Sheraton New York (color), Apr 29, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars I (folder 1 of 2) (b&w), Feb 1982 (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars I (folder 2 of 2) (b&w), Feb 1982 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars I: Announcement at Cocktail Party, Helmsley Palace (b&w), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars I: Program (photographs used or shot for) (b&w, sepia), 1982 (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars II (color), Apr 20, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars II: ABC Network Publicity Photographs (b&w), Mar 10, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars III: Headshots and Accompanying Biographical Sketches of Celebrity Participants: A-D (b&w), May 5, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars III: Headshots and Accompanying Biographical Sketches of Celebrity Participants: E-H (b&w), May 5, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars III: Headshots and Accompanying Biographical Sketches of Celebrity Participants: I-R (b&w), May 5, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - Gala: Night of 100 Stars III: Headshots and Accompanying Biographical Sketches of Celebrity Participants: S-W (b&w), May 5, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - Gala: "Razzle Dazzle" Gala (color), Nov 17, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 283)
    - Gala: Washington Gala, Washington, DC: Dinner at Statuary Hall (b&w), Oct 4, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - Gala: Washington Gala, Washington, DC: Dinner at Statuary Hall (folder 1 of 2) (color), Oct 4, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - Gala: Washington Gala, Washington, DC: Dinner at Statuary Hall (folder 2 of 2) (color), Oct 4, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - Gala: Washington Gala, Washington, DC: Event at Washington Hilton (b&w), Oct 5, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - Gala: Washington Gala, Washington DC: Event at Washington Hilton (color), Oct 5, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - Gala: Washington Gala, Washington, DC: Press Conference Announcement (b&w), Jun 30, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - Halloween Ball (2nd Annual) (color), Oct 27, 2000 (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Hollywood Squares Toasts Broadway (color), undated (Box 6, Folder 291)
    - Kensico Cemetery Monument (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - "Les Miserables": California Party (b&w), Aug 22, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 293)
    - Luncheon at Hotel Astor (b&w), Dec 19, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - Lunt Fontaine Theater, Renaming of (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - Lyceum Theater, Daniel Frohman's: Exterior and Interior (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - Night of Unsung Stars (b&w), 1985 (Box 6, Folder 297)
    - Notable Theatre Personalities Who Have Been Associated with the Actors' Fund (b&w), 1965-1971 (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - Palm View, West Hollywood, California (color), Sep 14, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - Palm View, West Hollywood, California (color), undated (Box 6, Folder 300)
    - Palm View, West Hollywood, California: Artist Rendering of Exterior (b&w), undated (Box 6, Folder 301)
    - Palm View, West Hollywood, California: Exterior & Interior (color), undated (Box 6, Folder 302)